<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<bookstore>
    <category>
        <name>COOKING</name>
        <book>
            <title>Everyday Italian</title>
            <author>Giada De Laurentiis</author>
            <year>2005</year>
            <price>30.00</price>
            <sold>1000</sold>
            <cover>cat1book1.jpg</cover>
            <description>
                Everyday Italian is a Food Network show hosted by Giada De Laurentiis. 
                In the show, De Laurentiis focuses for her viewers on traditional Italian cuisine with an American flair, 
                such as herb-crusted lamb and chocolate-ricotta pie.
            </description>
	</book>
        <book>
            <title>The Joy of Cooking</title>
            <author>Irma S. Rombauer</author>
            <author>Marion Rombauer Becker</author>
            <author>Ethan Becker</author>
            <year>1997</year>
            <price>50.00</price>
            <sold>2000</sold>
            <cover>cat1book2.jpg</cover>
            <description>
                Since its original publication, Joy of Cooking has been the most authoritative cookbook in America, 
                the one upon which millions of cooks have confidently relied for more than sixty-five years. 
                It's the book your grandmother and mother probably learned to cook from, 
                the book you gave your sister when she got married. 
                This, the first revision in more than twenty years, is better than ever. 
                Here's why: Every chapter has been rethought with an emphasis on freshness, convenience, and health.
            </description>
        </book>
        <book>
            <title>How to Cook Everything</title>
            <author> Mark Bittman</author>
            <year>1998</year>
            <price>39.99</price>
            <sold>1500</sold>
            <cover>cat1book3.jpg</cover>
            <description>
                Here's the breakthrough one-stop cooking reference for today's generation of cooks! 
                Nationally known cooking authority Mark Bittman shows you how to prepare great food 
                for all occasions using simple techniques, fresh ingredients, and basic kitchen equipment. 
                Just as important, How to Cook Everything takes a relaxed, straightforward approach to cooking, 
                so you can enjoy yourself in the kitchen and still achieve outstanding results.
            </description>
        </book>
    </category>
    <category>
        <name>CHILDREN</name>
        <book>
            <title>Harry Potter</title>
            <author>J K. Rowling</author>
            <year>2005</year>
            <sold>3000</sold>
            <price>29.99</price>
            <cover>cat2book1.jpg</cover>
            <description>
                Harry Potter is a series of fantasy novels written by British author J. K. Rowling. 
                The novels chronicle the life of a young wizard, Harry Potter, and his friends Hermione Granger and Ron Weasley, 
                all of whom are students at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. 
                The main story arc concerns Harry's struggle against Lord Voldemort, 
                the Dark wizard who intends to become immortal, overthrow the Ministry of Magic, 
                subjugate non-magic people and destroy anyone who stands in his way.
            </description>
	</book>
        <book>
            <title>Charlotte's Web</title>
            <author>E. B. White</author>
            <year>1952</year>
            <price>45.00</price>
            <sold>500</sold>
            <cover>cat2book2.png</cover>
            <description>
                Charlotte's Web is a children's novel by American author E. B. 
                White and illustrated by Garth Williams; it was published in October 15, 1952, by Harper Brothers. 
                The novel tells the story of a pig named Wilbur and his friendship with a barn spider named Charlotte. 
                When Wilbur is in danger of being slaughtered by the farmer, Charlotte writes messages praising Wilbur 
                (such as "Some Pig") in her web in order to persuade the farmer to let him live.
            </description>
        </book>
        <book>
            <title>The Hobbit</title>
            <author>J. R. R. Tolkie</author>
            <year>1937</year>
            <price>55.00</price>
            <cover>cat2book3.jpg</cover>
            <sold>2500</sold>
            <description>
                The Hobbit, or There and Back Again is a children's fantasy novel by English author J. R. R. Tolkien. 
                It was published on 21 September 1937 to wide critical acclaim, being nominated for the Carnegie Medal
                and awarded a prize from the New York Herald Tribune for best juvenile fiction. 
                The book remains popular and is recognized as a classic in children's literature.
            </description>
        </book>
    </category>
    <category>
        <name>WEB</name>
        <book>
            <title>XQuery Kick Start</title>
            <author>James McGovern</author>
            <author>Per Bothner</author>
            <author>Kurt Cagle</author>
            <author>James Linn</author>
            <author>Vaidyanathan Nagarajan</author>
            <year>2003</year>
            <price>49.99</price>
            <cover>cat3book1.jpg</cover>
            <sold>1300</sold>
            <description>
                XQuery Kick Start delivers a concise introduction to the XQuery standard, 
                and useful implementation advice for developers needing to put it into practice. 
                The book starts by explaining the role of XQuery in the XML family of specifications, 
                and its relationship with XPath. 
            </description>
        </book>
        <book>
            <title>Learning XML</title>
            <author>Erik T. Ray</author>
            <year>2003</year>
            <price>39.95</price>
            <cover>cat3book2.gif</cover>
            <sold>2100</sold>
            <description>
                This second edition of the bestselling Learning XML provides web developers with a 
                concise but grounded understanding of XML (the Extensible Markup Language) 
                and its potential-- not just a whirlwind tour of XML.The author explains the important
                and relevant XML technologies and their capabilities clearly and succinctly with plenty 
                of real-life projects and useful examples. He outlines the elements of markup--demystifying 
                concepts such as attributes, entities, and namespaces--and provides enough depth and 
                examples to get started.
            </description>
        </book>
    </category>
    <category>
        <name>SPORT</name>
        <book>
            <title>Eight men out</title>
            <author>Eliot Asinof</author>
            <year>1963</year>
            <price>49.95</price>
            <cover>cat4book1.jpg</cover>
            <sold>1100</sold>
            <description>
                First published in 1963, Eight Men Out has become a timeless classic. 
                Eliot Asinof has reconstructed the entire scene-by-scene story of the fantastic scandal 
                in which eight Chicago White Sox players arranged with the nation's leading 
                gamblers to throw the Series in Cincinnati. Mr. Asinof vividly describes the tense meetings, 
                the hitches in the conniving, the actual plays in which the Series was thrown, 
                the Grand Jury indictment, and the famous 1921 trial. 
            </description>
        </book>
        <book>
            <title>League of Denial</title>
            <author>Mark Fainaru-Wada</author>
            <author>Steve Fainaru</author>
            <year>2003</year>
            <price>59.00</price>
            <cover>cat4book2.jpg</cover>
            <sold>2500</sold>
            <description>
                League of Denial is a 2013 book, initially broadcast as a documentary film, 
                about traumatic brain injury in the National Football League (NFL), 
                particularly concussions and chronic traumatic encephalopathy (CTE). The documentary, 
                entitled League of Denial: The NFL's Concussion Crisis, was produced by Frontline and broadcast on PBS.
            </description>
        </book>
        <book>
            <title>The Game</title>
            <author>Ken Dryden</author>
            <year>2003</year>
            <price>29.95</price>
            <cover>cat4book3.jpg</cover>
            <sold>900</sold>
            <description>
                The Game is a book written by former ice hockey goaltender Ken Dryden. 
                Published in 1983, the book is a non-fiction account of the 1978-79 Montreal Canadiens, 
                detailing the life of a professional hockey player. The book describes the pressures of being
                a goaltender in the NHL, and gives readers a behind-the-scenes look at a team that would 
                eventually win the 1979 Stanley Cup.
            </description>
        </book>
    </category>
</bookstore>